{"url": "https://www.aera.net/Newsroom/Trending-Topic-Research-Files/Trending-Topic-Research-File-Education-Technology-and-Online-Learning", "word_count": 5055, "entities": [{"text": "Trending Topic Research File\nEducators", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "AERA", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2002", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Limitations", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "District Digital Capacity for Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Emily E. N. Miller", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sarah Pedersen AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2024", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "nonmetropolitan", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Louisiana", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "September 2024", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Louisiana", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Learning Together", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Scott A. Pattison", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gina Svarovsky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Viviana López Burgos", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Alicia Santiago", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Sarah McGrew", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Joel Breakstone AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Dorottya Demszky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jing Liu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Heather C. Hill", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Jurafsky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Piech Educational Evaluation", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "M-Powering Teachers", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kenna Hernly", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jason C. Yip", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniel Pauw", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Caroline Pitt", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "April 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Science Everywhere", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Craig A. Mason", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ji-Eun Lee", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jenny Yun-Chen Chan", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Adam Sales", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Allison Liu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shihfen Tu AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "April 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "DragonBox", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "the United States", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Carla C. Johnson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Janet B. Walton", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lacey Strickler", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Brammer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "August 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "K–12", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Digital Media Resources", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "PBS", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Claire G. Christensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elisa B. Garcia", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Janna F. Kook", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Naomi Hupert", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Phil Vahey", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "July 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Joan Kang Shin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jered Borup", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael K. Barbour", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "AERA Open", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "April 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Christopher J. Buttimer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Justin Reich AERA", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "4-month", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Anna D. Johnson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Owen N. Schochet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sherri Castle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Diane Horm", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Sorting Machines", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Digital Technology", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Cassidy Puckett Educational", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Broadband Access", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Student Opportunities", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Susan Kemper Patrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jason A. Grissom", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "S. Colby Woods", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Germany", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susanne Enke", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Verena E. Johann", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julia Karbach", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Henrik Saalbach", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kara M. Gavin AERA", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "10-year-old", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "COVID-19", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Stephen J. Aguilar", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Hernan Galperin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Clare Baek", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Rachel Baker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Qiujie Li", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gabe Avakian", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Orona", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mark Warschauer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "4-year", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Remote Learning", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "COVID-19", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Houston", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Texas", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "October 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Latinx", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Michael Noetel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shantell Griffith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Oscar Delaney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicola Rose Harris", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Philip Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Borja", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Neuroscience Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Ido Davidesco", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Camillia Matuk", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dana Bevilacqua", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "David Poeppel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Students Attending School", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Suffer Socially", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Angela L. Duckworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tim Kautz", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Amy Defnet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sean Talamas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Benjamin Lira", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Stanton Wortham", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katrina Borowiec", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Samantha Ha", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephanie Carroll", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lizhou Wang", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julie Kim AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Student Learning in", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Stephanie Riegg Cellini", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Hernando Grueso", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Colombia", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Carolyn J. Heinrich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "4-year", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis Jane Lee", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Devan Antczak", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rhiannon Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael Noetel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "March 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Video Improves Learning", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Michael Noetel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shantell Griffith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Oscar Delaney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Borja", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "February 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Logics Collide", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Iris Daruwala", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shani Bretas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "U.S.", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Julie Cohen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Vivian Wong", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rebekah Berlin Educational", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "February 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Reassessing Disparities", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Higher Education Justin Paulsen", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Screens", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Apps", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Adriana G. Bus", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susan B. Neuman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kathleen Roskos AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Improve Phonological Awareness", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Writing", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lieny Jeon", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Yolanda Abel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "3 months", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "three additional days", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jeffrey A. Greene", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rebekah Freed", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Brian M. Cartiff", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Cynthia Demetriou", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "A. T. Panter", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Patrick Holschuh Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "May 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth,", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Sorensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Walters", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jordan Rickles", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jessica B. Heppen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elaine Allensworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicholas Sorensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kirk Walters Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Nicole Shechtman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jeremy Roschelle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mingyu Feng", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Corinne Singleton AERA Open", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Organizing Shared Digital Reading", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Groups", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "the Affordances of Text and Medium Trude Hoel", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Computerized Electronic Features Direct Children’s Attention", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Sridhar Priyashri AERA", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Outcomes Tanya Christ", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "X. Christine Wang", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ming Ming Chiu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ekaterina Strekalova-Hughes AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Educational and Fun", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Versus Preschooler Perceptions", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Digital", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Gabrielle A. Strouse", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lisa A. Newland", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniel J. Mourlam AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Digital", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Print", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Joanna C. Yau", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ying Xu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tallin Muskat", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jessica Uvalle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniela Cannata AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "SMART", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Develop", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "James S. Kim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Catherine A. Asher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mary Burkhauser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Laura Mesite", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Diana Leyva AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Digital Versus Paper Reading Processes and Links to Comprehension for Middle School Students Amanda", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "P. Goodwin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sun-Joo Cho", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Dan Reynolds", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katherine Brady", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jorge Salas American", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Digital Early Spelling Game", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Dorit Aram AERA Open", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Outcomes Carolyn J. Heinrich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Annalee Good", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Cheng American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "March 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Online Learning", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Berger", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Brian Jacob", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susanna Loeb", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael Hill", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "February 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Mooresville", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Marie Hull", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katherine Duch Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "September 2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jessica B. Heppen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elaine Allensworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicholas Sorensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kirk Walters Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Sarah Dryden-Peterson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Negin Dahya", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elizabeth Adelman American Educational Research Journal", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Bronfenbrenner", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "We Model Learning", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Systematic Review of Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Srećko Joksimović", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Oleksandra Poquet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Vitomir Kovanović", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nia Dowell", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Caitlin Mills", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shane Dawson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Arthur C. Graesser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Christopher Brooks Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Amy Stornaiuolo", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elizabeth Thomas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "June 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the Multimodal Public Sphere Nicole Mirra", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Antero Garcia Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "June 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Student Enrollment Patterns and", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Achievement", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Ohio", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Andrew McEachin Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "White", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Lindsay Woodward", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Li", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Wendy Barlow American", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Digital Games", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Douglas B. Clark", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Emily E. Tanner-Smith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephen S. Killingsworth Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Austin Beck", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "John Rice", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michelle Foster AERA Open", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "FIM", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Grades", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "FIM", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Improving Access", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Effectiveness", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Digital Tutoring", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "K–12 Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Patricia Burch", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Annalee Good", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Carolyn Heinrich Educational", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "K–12", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Jeremy Roschelle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mingyu Feng", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Robert F. Murphy", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Craig A. Mason", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the-year", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Investigating Technology-Enhanced Teacher Professional Development", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Catherine E. LePrevost", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "A. Dell Tolin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kristie S. Gutierrez Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "April 2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Pitfalls", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Interactive Features", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Zsofia K. Takacs", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elise K. Swart", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Adriana G. Bus Review of Educational Research", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2015", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis of", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Abbey C. Karich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Matthew K. Burns", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kathrin E. Maki", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Computer-Based Science Inquiry Learning Environments for Precollege Students Dermot F. Donnelly", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Marcia C. Linn", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sten Ludvigsen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Teachers Choosing Rich Tasks", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Peter Aubusson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Paul Burke", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sandy Schuck", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Matthew Kearney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Bart Frischknecht Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Discrete Choice Experiments", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Mina Johnson-Glenberg Educational", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2013", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "The State of Wiki Usage", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "U.S.", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Justin Reich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Richard Murnane", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "John Willett Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2012", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "The Effectiveness of Distance Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Virginia", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Di Xu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shanna Smith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "April 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Forty Years", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the Impact of Technology on Learning", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Rana M. Tamim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Robert M. Bernard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eugene Borokhovski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Richard F. Schmid Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "40 years", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "New Technology", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Digital Worlds: Analyzing Evidence of Equity in Access", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Outcomes Mark Warschauer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tina Matuchniak Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2010", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the New Literacy Studies", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kathy Ann Mills", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2010", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Integration of Technology", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Professional Development for Advancing Middle School Mathematics", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Jeremy Roschelle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicole Shechtman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Deborah Tatar", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephen Hegedus", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Bill Hopkins", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susan Empson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Knudsen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lawrence P. Gallagher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2010", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "SimCalc", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis of", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Robert M. Bernard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eugene Borokhovski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "C. Anne Wade", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rana M. Tamim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael A. Surkes", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Edward Clement Bethel Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "September 2009", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Professional Development in Integrating Technology Into Teaching and Learning", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Unknowns", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Ways to Pursue Better Questions and", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kimberly A. Lawless", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "James W. Pellegrino Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2007", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Learning Anytime", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sigmund Tobias", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Robert A. Wisher Educational Researcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2007", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "ADL", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Mary K. Tallent-Runnels", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julie A. Thomas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "William Y. Lan", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sandi Cooper", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Terence C. Ahern", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shana M. Shaw", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Xiaoming Liu Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Spring 2006", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Going the Distance With Online Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Jorge Larreamendy-Joerns", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gaea Leinhardt Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Winter 2006", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis of the Empirical Literature", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Robert M. Bernard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lou", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Evgueni Borokhovski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Anne Wade", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lori Wozney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Peter Andrew Wallet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Fiset Binru", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Huang Review", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Fall 2004", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Wallace American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Summer 2004", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Factors Affecting Technology Uses", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Yong Zhao", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kenneth A. Frank American Educational Research Journal", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2003", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Daniel T. Hickey", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ann C. H. Kindfield", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Paul Horwitz", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mary Ann T. Christie", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2003", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Transformation", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Barbara Means", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jeremy Roschelle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "William Penuel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nora Sabelli", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Geneva Haertel Review of Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "January 2003", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Tracing Teachers’ Use of Technology", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Beliefs, Social Dynamics", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kurt Sahl", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Spring 2002", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Larry Cuban", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Heather Kirkpatrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Craig Peck American Educational Research Journal", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2001", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Small Group", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Individual Learning with Technology", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Meta-Analysis Yiping Lou", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sylvia d’Apollonia Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Fall 2001", "label": "DATE"}], "relations": [{"source": "AERA", "target": "2002", "sentence": "The following compendium of open-access articles are inclusive of all substantive AERA journal content regarding education technology and online learning published since 2002."}, {"source": "Limitations", "target": "District Digital Capacity for Education", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "District Digital Capacity for Education", "target": "Emily E. N. Miller", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "Emily E. N. Miller", "target": "Sarah Pedersen AERA Open", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "Sarah Pedersen AERA Open", "target": "December 2024", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "Louisiana", "target": "September 2024", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024"}, {"source": "Learning Together", "target": "Scott A. Pattison", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Scott A. Pattison", "target": "Gina Svarovsky", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Gina Svarovsky", "target": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "target": "Viviana López Burgos", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Viviana López Burgos", "target": "Alicia Santiago", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Alicia Santiago", "target": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "target": "October 2023", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Sarah McGrew", "target": "Joel Breakstone AERA Open", "sentence": "Sarah McGrew, Joel Breakstone AERA Open, June 2023"}, {"source": "Joel Breakstone AERA Open", "target": "June 2023", "sentence": "Sarah McGrew, Joel Breakstone AERA Open, June 2023"}, {"source": "Dorottya Demszky", "target": "Jing Liu", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Jing Liu", "target": "Heather C. Hill", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Heather C. Hill", "target": "Dan Jurafsky", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Dan Jurafsky", "target": "Chris Piech Educational Evaluation", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Chris Piech Educational Evaluation", "target": "May 2023", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Kenna Hernly", "target": "Jason C. Yip", "sentence": "Changing Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023"}, {"source": "Jason C. Yip", "target": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "sentence": "Changing Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023"}, {"source": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "target": "Daniel Pauw", "sentence": "Changing Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023"}, {"source": "Daniel Pauw", "target": "Caroline Pitt", "sentence": "Changing Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023"}, {"source": "Caroline Pitt", "target": "April 2023", "sentence": "Changing Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023"}, {"source": "Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow", "target": "Craig A. Mason", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Craig A. Mason", "target": "Ji-Eun Lee", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Ji-Eun Lee", "target": "Jenny Yun-Chen Chan", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Jenny Yun-Chen Chan", "target": "Adam Sales", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Adam Sales", "target": "Allison Liu", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Allison Liu", "target": "Shihfen Tu AERA Open", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Shihfen Tu AERA Open", "target": "April 2023", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "the United States", "target": "Carla C. Johnson", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "Carla C. Johnson", "target": "Janet B. Walton", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "Janet B. Walton", "target": "Lacey Strickler", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "Lacey Strickler", "target": "Jennifer Brammer", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "Jennifer Brammer", "target": "August 2022", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "August 2022", "target": "K–12", "sentence": "Online Teaching in K-12 Education in the United States: A Systematic Review Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research, August 2022 Researchers found that set of contextual conditions that are foundational to student learning in K–12 online settings (prepared educators, technology access and autonomy, students’ developmental needs and abilities, and students’ self-regulated learning skills).\n"}, {"source": "Digital Media Resources", "target": "PBS", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS"}, {"source": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy", "target": "Claire G. Christensen", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Claire G. Christensen", "target": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "target": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "target": "Elisa B. Garcia", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Elisa B. Garcia", "target": "Janna F. Kook", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Janna F. Kook", "target": "Naomi Hupert", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Naomi Hupert", "target": "Phil Vahey", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Phil Vahey", "target": "Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal", "target": "July 2022", "sentence": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022 Researchers examined whether free educational videos and digital games supported children’s ability to use informational text to answer real-world questions.\n"}, {"source": "Joan Kang Shin", "target": "Jered Borup", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Jered Borup", "target": "Michael K. Barbour", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Michael K. Barbour", "target": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "target": "AERA Open", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "AERA Open", "target": "April 2022", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Christopher J. Buttimer", "target": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA"}, {"source": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "target": "Justin Reich AERA", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA"}, {"source": "January 2022", "target": "4-month", "sentence": "Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey.\n"}, {"source": "First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19", "target": "Anna D. Johnson", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Anna D. Johnson", "target": "Owen N. Schochet", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Owen N. Schochet", "target": "Sherri Castle", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Sherri Castle", "target": "Diane Horm", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Diane Horm", "target": "Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open", "target": "January 2022", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022"}, {"source": "Sorting Machines", "target": "Digital Technology", "sentence": "Sorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar.\n"}, {"source": "Digital Technology", "target": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "sentence": "Sorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar.\n"}, {"source": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "target": "Cassidy Puckett Educational", "sentence": "Sorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar.\n"}, {"source": "Cassidy Puckett Educational", "target": "January 2022", "sentence": "Sorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar.\n"}, {"source": "Broadband Access", "target": "Student Opportunities", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Student Opportunities", "target": "Susan Kemper Patrick", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Susan Kemper Patrick", "target": "Jason A. Grissom", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Jason A. Grissom", "target": "S. Colby Woods", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "S. Colby Woods", "target": "UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open", "target": "December 2021", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Germany", "target": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "target": "Susanne Enke", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Susanne Enke", "target": "Verena E. Johann", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Verena E. Johann", "target": "Julia Karbach", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Julia Karbach", "target": "Henrik Saalbach", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Henrik Saalbach", "target": "December 2021", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices", "target": "Kara M. Gavin AERA", "sentence": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices Kara M. Gavin AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Kara M. Gavin AERA", "target": "December 2021", "sentence": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices Kara M. Gavin AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "10-year-old", "target": "COVID-19", "sentence": "Researchers examined ways in which a diverse group of 9- and 10-year-old children resisted the isolating circumstances early in the COVID-19 pandemic through creating and repurposing digital spaces to connect with friends, classmates, and family members.\n"}, {"source": "Stephen J. Aguilar", "target": "Hernan Galperin", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021 Researchers found a strong correlation between live instruction and student engagement in online learning among elementary school students, with every additional hour of live instruction per week increasing the probability of reporting that students have completed all their schoolwork by 26%.\n"}, {"source": "Hernan Galperin", "target": "Clare Baek", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021 Researchers found a strong correlation between live instruction and student engagement in online learning among elementary school students, with every additional hour of live instruction per week increasing the probability of reporting that students have completed all their schoolwork by 26%.\n"}, {"source": "Clare Baek", "target": "Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021 Researchers found a strong correlation between live instruction and student engagement in online learning among elementary school students, with every additional hour of live instruction per week increasing the probability of reporting that students have completed all their schoolwork by 26%.\n"}, {"source": "Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher", "target": "November 2021", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021 Researchers found a strong correlation between live instruction and student engagement in online learning among elementary school students, with every additional hour of live instruction per week increasing the probability of reporting that students have completed all their schoolwork by 26%.\n"}, {"source": "Rachel Baker", "target": "Qiujie Li", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "Qiujie Li", "target": "Gabe Avakian", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "Gabe Avakian", "target": "Orona", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "Orona", "target": "Mark Warschauer", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "Mark Warschauer", "target": "November 2021", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "November 2021", "target": "4-year", "sentence": "Increasing Success in Higher Education: The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021 Researchers found that online course taking of major-required courses leads to higher likelihood of successful 4-year graduation and slightly accelerated time-to-degree."}, {"source": "Remote Learning", "target": "COVID-19", "sentence": "Remote Learning, COVID-19, and Children With Disabilities Kate Henley Averett AERA"}, {"source": "Houston", "target": "Texas", "sentence": "Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021 Researchers found that Latinx families made schooling decisions informed by their shared school context, the needs of family networks, and community infection rates.\n"}, {"source": "Texas", "target": "October 2021", "sentence": "Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021 Researchers found that Latinx families made schooling decisions informed by their shared school context, the needs of family networks, and community infection rates.\n"}, {"source": "October 2021", "target": "Latinx", "sentence": "Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021 Researchers found that Latinx families made schooling decisions informed by their shared school context, the needs of family networks, and community infection rates.\n"}, {"source": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis", "target": "Michael Noetel", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "target": "Shantell Griffith", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Shantell Griffith", "target": "Oscar Delaney", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Oscar Delaney", "target": "Nicola Rose Harris", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Nicola Rose Harris", "target": "Philip Parker", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "target": "Borja", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Borja", "target": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "target": "October 2021", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021 Researchers found 11 design principles that demonstrated significant, positive, meta-analytic effects on learning and five that significantly improved management of cognitive load.\n"}, {"source": "Neuroscience Research", "target": "Ido Davidesco", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "Ido Davidesco", "target": "Camillia Matuk", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "Camillia Matuk", "target": "Dana Bevilacqua", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "Dana Bevilacqua", "target": "David Poeppel", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "David Poeppel", "target": "Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher", "target": "July 2021", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers evaluated the value added by portable brain technologies in education research and outlines a proposed research agenda, centered around questions related to student engagement, cognitive load, and self-regulation.\n"}, {"source": "Students Attending School", "target": "Suffer Socially", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Suffer Socially", "target": "Angela L. Duckworth", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Angela L. Duckworth", "target": "Tim Kautz", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Tim Kautz", "target": "Amy Defnet", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Amy Defnet", "target": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "target": "Sean Talamas", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Sean Talamas", "target": "Benjamin Lira", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Benjamin Lira", "target": "Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher", "target": "July 2021", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021 Researchers found that high school students who attended school remotely reported lower levels of social, emotional, and academic well-being than classmates who attended school in person.\n"}, {"source": "Stanton Wortham", "target": "Katrina Borowiec", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Katrina Borowiec", "target": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "target": "Samantha Ha", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Samantha Ha", "target": "Stephanie Carroll", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Stephanie Carroll", "target": "Lizhou Wang", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Lizhou Wang", "target": "Julie Kim AERA Open", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Julie Kim AERA Open", "target": "May 2021", "sentence": "Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found three teaching approaches that faculty used to achieve formative education online: empathic (centering students’ emotions), reflective (facilitating deep inquiry), and adaptive (having flexibility in meeting students’ needs).\n"}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "target": "May 2021", "sentence": ": Student–Teacher Congruence in Online, High School Courses Jennifer Darling-Aduana AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found that students belonging to marginalized groups experience positive impacts when taught by a teacher of the same race, ethnicity, and gender.\n"}, {"source": "Student Learning in", "target": "Stephanie Riegg Cellini", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found that while online students perform significantly worse than on-campus students on exit exams in private institutions, they perform better in SENA—the main public vocational institution in Colombia.\n"}, {"source": "Stephanie Riegg Cellini", "target": "Hernando Grueso", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found that while online students perform significantly worse than on-campus students on exit exams in private institutions, they perform better in SENA—the main public vocational institution in Colombia.\n"}, {"source": "Hernando Grueso", "target": "May 2021", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found that while online students perform significantly worse than on-campus students on exit exams in private institutions, they perform better in SENA—the main public vocational institution in Colombia.\n"}, {"source": "May 2021", "target": "Colombia", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021 Researchers found that while online students perform significantly worse than on-campus students on exit exams in private institutions, they perform better in SENA—the main public vocational institution in Colombia.\n"}, {"source": "Carolyn J. Heinrich", "target": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational", "sentence": "Carolyn J. Heinrich, Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, March 2021 Researchers found that positive associations between online course-taking, credits earned and high school graduation, and for those with limited online course-taking, small increases in college enrollment."}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational", "target": "March 2021", "sentence": "Carolyn J. Heinrich, Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, March 2021 Researchers found that positive associations between online course-taking, credits earned and high school graduation, and for those with limited online course-taking, small increases in college enrollment."}, {"source": "Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis", "target": "Meta-Analysis Jane Lee", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Meta-Analysis Jane Lee", "target": "Devan Antczak", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Devan Antczak", "target": "Rhiannon Parker", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Rhiannon Parker", "target": "Michael Noetel", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "target": "Philip Parker", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "target": "Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research", "target": "March 2021", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021 Researchers found that course design and employers’ provision of time to complete learning are key for engaging learners.\n"}, {"source": "Video Improves Learning", "target": "Michael Noetel", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "target": "Shantell Griffith", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Shantell Griffith", "target": "Oscar Delaney", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Oscar Delaney", "target": "Philip Parker", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "target": "Borja", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Borja", "target": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale Review", "target": "February 2021", "sentence": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021 Although results may be subject to some experimental and publication biases, they suggest that videos are unlikely to be detrimental and usually improve student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Logics Collide", "target": "Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization", "target": "Iris Daruwala", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Iris Daruwala", "target": "Shani Bretas", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Shani Bretas", "target": "Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher", "target": "September 2020", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "September 2020", "target": "U.S.", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020 Using the adoption of a personalized, blended learning mathematics program at five U.S. schools as a case study, researchers describe how teachers, school leaders, and program staff navigated institutional pressures to improve state grade-level standardized test scores while implementing tasks and technologies designed to personalize student learning.\n"}, {"source": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access", "target": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "sentence": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access in High Schools Jennifer Darling-Aduana, Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher, June 2020 Findings from fixed effects models indicate improved access to advanced courses and higher ACT scores among students enrolled in telepresence courses.\n"}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "target": "Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher", "sentence": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access in High Schools Jennifer Darling-Aduana, Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher, June 2020 Findings from fixed effects models indicate improved access to advanced courses and higher ACT scores among students enrolled in telepresence courses.\n"}, {"source": "Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher", "target": "June 2020", "sentence": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access in High Schools Jennifer Darling-Aduana, Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher, June 2020 Findings from fixed effects models indicate improved access to advanced courses and higher ACT scores among students enrolled in telepresence courses.\n"}, {"source": "Julie Cohen", "target": "Vivian Wong", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020 Researchers found that coached candidates had significant and large improvements on skills relative to those who only reflected on their teaching.\n"}, {"source": "Vivian Wong", "target": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020 Researchers found that coached candidates had significant and large improvements on skills relative to those who only reflected on their teaching.\n"}, {"source": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "target": "Rebekah Berlin Educational", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020 Researchers found that coached candidates had significant and large improvements on skills relative to those who only reflected on their teaching.\n"}, {"source": "Rebekah Berlin Educational", "target": "February 2020", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020 Researchers found that coached candidates had significant and large improvements on skills relative to those who only reflected on their teaching.\n"}, {"source": "Reassessing Disparities", "target": "Higher Education Justin Paulsen", "sentence": "Reassessing Disparities in Online Learner Student Engagement in Higher Education Justin Paulsen, Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher, January 2020"}, {"source": "Higher Education Justin Paulsen", "target": "Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher", "sentence": "Reassessing Disparities in Online Learner Student Engagement in Higher Education Justin Paulsen, Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher, January 2020"}, {"source": "Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher", "target": "January 2020", "sentence": "Reassessing Disparities in Online Learner Student Engagement in Higher Education Justin Paulsen, Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher, January 2020"}, {"source": "Screens", "target": "Apps", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Apps", "target": "Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia", "target": "Adriana G. Bus", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Adriana G. Bus", "target": "Susan B. Neuman", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Susan B. Neuman", "target": "Kathleen Roskos AERA Open", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Kathleen Roskos AERA Open", "target": "2020", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Improve Phonological Awareness", "target": "Writing", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Writing", "target": "Lieny Jeon", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Lieny Jeon", "target": "Yolanda Abel", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Yolanda Abel", "target": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "target": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "target": "2020", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020"}, {"source": "Jeffrey A. Greene", "target": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "target": "Rebekah Freed", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Rebekah Freed", "target": "Brian M. Cartiff", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Brian M. Cartiff", "target": "Cynthia Demetriou", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Cynthia Demetriou", "target": "A. T. Panter", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "A. T. Panter", "target": "July 2019", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Patrick Holschuh Review", "target": "Education", "sentence": "Teaching Academically Underprepared Postsecondary Students Dolores Perin, Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education, May 2019 This chapter discusses approaches to the teaching of academically underprepared postsecondary students and how teaching might be changed to improve student outcomes.\n"}, {"source": "Education", "target": "May 2019", "sentence": "Teaching Academically Underprepared Postsecondary Students Dolores Perin, Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education, May 2019 This chapter discusses approaches to the teaching of academically underprepared postsecondary students and how teaching might be changed to improve student outcomes.\n"}, {"source": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth,", "target": "Sorensen", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019 Researchers discuss whether it would have been appropriate to test for nominally equivalent outcomes, given that the study was initially conceived and designed to test for significant differences, and that the conclusion of no difference was not solely based on a null hypothesis test.\n"}, {"source": "Sorensen", "target": "Walters", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019 Researchers discuss whether it would have been appropriate to test for nominally equivalent outcomes, given that the study was initially conceived and designed to test for significant differences, and that the conclusion of no difference was not solely based on a null hypothesis test.\n"}, {"source": "Walters", "target": "2018", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019 Researchers discuss whether it would have been appropriate to test for nominally equivalent outcomes, given that the study was initially conceived and designed to test for significant differences, and that the conclusion of no difference was not solely based on a null hypothesis test.\n"}, {"source": "2018", "target": "Jordan Rickles", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019 Researchers discuss whether it would have been appropriate to test for nominally equivalent outcomes, given that the study was initially conceived and designed to test for significant differences, and that the conclusion of no difference was not solely based on a null hypothesis test.\n"}, {"source": "Jordan Rickles", "target": "Jessica B. Heppen", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas 