{"url": "https://www.aera.net/Newsroom/Trending-Topic-Research-Files/Trending-Topic-Research-File-Education-Technology-and-Online-Learning", "domain": "www.aera.net", "word_count": 5055, "entities": [{"text": "AERA", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2002", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Emily E. N. Miller", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sarah Pedersen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2024", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Louisiana", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Shirin Hashim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2024", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "third through fifth grade", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Scott A. Pattison", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gina Svarovsky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Viviana López Burgos", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Alicia Santiago", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Sarah McGrew", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Joel Breakstone", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Dorottya Demszky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jing Liu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Heather C. Hill", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Jurafsky", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Piech", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Changing Lanes:", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Tamara Clegg", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kenna Hernly", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June Ahn", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jason C. Yip", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniel Pauw", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Caroline Pitt", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "American Educational Research Journal", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "April 2023", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Craig A. Mason", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ji-Eun Lee", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Yun-Chen Chan", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Adam Sales", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Allison Liu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shihfen Tu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "From Here to There", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "the United States", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Carla C. Johnson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Janet B. Walton", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lacey Strickler", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Brammer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elliott Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "August 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Molly", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "PBS", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Claire G. Christensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elisa B. Garcia", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Janna F. Kook", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Naomi Hupert", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Phil Vahey", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shelley Pasnik", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Joan Kang Shin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jered Borup", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael K. Barbour", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "April 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "COVID", "label": "EVENT"}, {"text": "Christopher J. Buttimer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Justin Reich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2022", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "4-month", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Anna D. Johnson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Owen N. Schochet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sherri Castle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Diane Horm", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Deborah A. Phillips", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Cassidy Puckett", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susan Kemper Patrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jason A. Grissom", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "S. Colby Woods", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "UrLeaka W. Newsome", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the COVID-19 Pandemic", "label": "EVENT"}, {"text": "Germany", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susanne Enke", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Verena E. Johann", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julia Karbach", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Henrik Saalbach", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Curating Spaces of Connection", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Kara M. Gavin", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "10-year-old", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Stephen J. Aguilar", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Hernan Galperin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Clare Baek", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eduardo Gonzalez", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Christian Fischer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rachel Baker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Qiujie Li", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gabe Avakian Orona", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mark Warschauer", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "4-year", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Remote Learning", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Kate Henley", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Houston", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Texas", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Julia Szabo", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Michael Noetel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shantell Griffith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Oscar Delaney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicola Rose Harris", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Taren Sanders", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Borja del Pozo Cruz", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Chris Lonsdale", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Ido Davidesco", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Camillia Matuk", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dana Bevilacqua", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "David Poeppel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Suzanne Dikker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Angela L. Duckworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tim Kautz", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Amy Defnet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sean Talamas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Benjamin Lira", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Laurence Steinberg", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Deoksoon Kim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stanton Wortham", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katrina Borowiec", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Samantha Ha", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephanie Carroll", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lizhou Wang", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julie Kim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "May 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephanie Riegg Cellini", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Hernando Grueso", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "SENA", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Colombia", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Carolyn J. Heinrich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jane Lee", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Devan Antczak", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rhiannon Parker", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Video Improves Learning in Higher Education: A Systematic Review", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "February 2021", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "When Logics Collide: Implementing", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Iris Daruwala", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shani Bretas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Douglas D. Ready", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "U.S.", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Carolyn Heinrich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Julie Cohen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Vivian Wong", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rebekah Berlin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "February 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Justin Paulsen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Alexander C. McCormick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Susan B. Neuman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kathleen Roskos", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2020", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Escribo", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Americo N. Amorim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lieny Jeon", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Yolanda Abel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Natália Martins Dias", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "3 months", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "November 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "three additional days", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jeffrey A. Greene", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Rebekah Freed", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Brian M. Cartiff", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Cynthia Demetriou", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "A. T. Panter", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "July 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Dolores Perin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "May 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Rickles", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Heppen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Allensworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sorensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Walters", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Jordan Rickles", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jessica B. Heppen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elaine Allensworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nicholas Sorensen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kirk Walters", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "An Efficacy Study of a Digital Core Curriculum for Grade 5 Mathematics", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Nicole Shechtman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jeremy Roschelle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mingyu Feng", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Corinne Singleton", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Trude Hoel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elise Seip", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Show", "label": "EVENT"}, {"text": "W. Quin Yow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sridhar Priyashri", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tanya Christ", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "X. Christine Wang", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ming Ming Chiu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ekaterina Strekalova", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gabrielle A. Strouse", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lisa A. Newland", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniel J. Mourlam", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "AERA Open", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Stephanie M. Reich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Joanna C. Yau", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ying Xu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Tallin Muskat", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jessica Uvalle", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Daniela Cannata", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "James S. Kim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Catherine A. Asher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mary Burkhauser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Laura Mesite", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Diana Leyva", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Amanda P. Goodwin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sun-Joo Cho", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Reynolds", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katherine Brady", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jorge Salas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Adi Elimelech", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dorit Aram", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Annalee Good", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Huiping (Emily) Cheng", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Cassandra M. D. Hart", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Berger", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Brian Jacob", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susanna Loeb", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael Hill", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "February 2019", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Mooresville’s Digital Conversion Initiative", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Marie Hull", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Katherine Duch Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "September 2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "July 2018", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Connecting Locally and Globally Situated Resources", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Sarah Dryden-Peterson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Negin Dahya", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elizabeth Adelman", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "December 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Bronfenbrenner", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "A Systematic Review of Research on MOOCs", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Srećko Joksimović", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Oleksandra Poquet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Vitomir Kovanović", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nia Dowell", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Caitlin Mills", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dragan Gašević", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shane Dawson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Arthur C. Graesser", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Christopher Brooks Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "November 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Disrupting Educational Inequalities Through Youth Digital Activism", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Amy Stornaiuolo", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ebony Elizabeth Thomas Review of Research in Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "June 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Civic Participation Reimagined: Youth Interrogation and Innovation in the Multimodal Public Sphere", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Nicole Mirra", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Antero Garcia Review of Research in Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Ohio", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "June", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Andrew McEachin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "January 2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Byeong-Young Cho", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lindsay Woodward", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Dan Li", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Wendy Barlow", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2017", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Path", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Digital Games, Design, and Learning: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Douglas B. Clark", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Emily E. Tanner-Smith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephen S. Killingsworth", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "June Ahn", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Austin Beck", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "John Rice", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michelle Foster", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Improving Access to, Quality, and the Effectiveness of Digital Tutoring", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Patricia Burch", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Carolyn Heinrich", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Robert F. Murphy", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "October 2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Margaret R. Blanchard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Catherine E. LePrevost", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "A. Dell Tolin", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kristie S. Gutierrez", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "April 2016", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Zsofia K. Takacs", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Elise K. Swart", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Adriana G. Bus", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2015", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Abbey C. Karich", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Matthew K. Burns", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kathrin E. Maki Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "September 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Dermot F. Donnelly", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Marcia C. Linn", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sten Ludvigsen Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "December 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Peter Aubusson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Paul Burke", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sandy Schuck", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Matthew Kearney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Bart Frischknecht", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "June 2014", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Robb Lindgren", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mina Johnson-Glenberg", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "November 2013", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Richard Murnane", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "John Willett", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2012", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Virginia", "label": "GPE"}, {"text": "Di Xu", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shanna Smith", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "September 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "The Lecture as a Transmedial Pedagogical Form", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "April 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Franzel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Forty Years", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Rana M. Tamim", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Robert M. Bernard", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Eugene Borokhovski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Richard F. Schmid", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "March 2011", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "40 years", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "New Technology and Digital Worlds: Analyzing Evidence of Equity in Access, Use, and Outcomes", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Tina Matuchniak Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "2010", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "the New Literacy Studies", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Deborah Tatar", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Stephen Hegedus", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Bill Hopkins", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Susan Empson", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Jennifer Knudsen", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lawrence P. Gallagher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "C. Anne Wade", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Michael A. Surkes", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Edward Clement Bethel Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "September 2009", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Kimberly A. Lawless", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "James W. Pellegrino Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "December 2007", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Learning Anytime, Anywhere:", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "J. D. Fletcher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sigmund Tobias", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Robert A. Wisher", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "March 2007", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Teaching Courses Online", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Mary K. Tallent-Runnels", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Julie A. Thomas", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "William Y. Lan", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sandi Cooper", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Terence C. Ahern", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Shana M. Shaw", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Xiaoming Liu Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Spring 2006", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Going the Distance With Online Education", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Jorge Larreamendy-Joerns", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Gaea Leinhardt Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Winter 2006", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Philip C. Abrami Yiping Lou", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Evgueni Borokhovski", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Anne Wade", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Lori Wozney", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Peter Andrew Wallet", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Manon Fiset", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Fall 2004", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Raven McCrory Wallace", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Summer 2004", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Yong Zhao", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kenneth A. Frank", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2003", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Integrating Curriculum, Instruction, Assessment, and Evaluation", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Daniel T. Hickey", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Ann C. H. Kindfield", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Paul Horwitz", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Mary Ann T. Christie", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Barbara Means", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "William Penuel", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Nora Sabelli", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Geneva Haertel Review of Research in Education", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "January 2003", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Tracing Teachers’ Use of Technology", "label": "WORK_OF_ART"}, {"text": "Mark Windschitl", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Kurt Sahl", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Spring 2002", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Larry Cuban", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Heather Kirkpatrick", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Craig Peck", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "2001", "label": "DATE"}, {"text": "Yiping Lou", "label": "PERSON"}, {"text": "Sylvia d’Apollonia Review of Educational Research", "label": "ORG"}, {"text": "Fall 2001", "label": "DATE"}], "relations": [{"source": "AERA", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "2002", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "The following compendium of open-access articles are inclusive of all substantive AERA journal content regarding education technology and online learning published since 2002."}, {"source": "Emily E. N. Miller", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sarah Pedersen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "Sarah Pedersen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "December 2024", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Promises and Limitations in District Digital Capacity for Education During COVID-19 Emily E. N. Miller, Sarah Pedersen AERA Open, December 2024"}, {"source": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Louisiana", "target_label": "GPE", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024 This study examines the impact of an online math learning program on third through fifth grade math achievement in Louisiana."}, {"source": "Louisiana", "source_label": "GPE", "target": "Shirin Hashim", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024 This study examines the impact of an online math learning program on third through fifth grade math achievement in Louisiana."}, {"source": "Shirin Hashim", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "September 2024", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024 This study examines the impact of an online math learning program on third through fifth grade math achievement in Louisiana."}, {"source": "September 2024", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "third through fifth grade", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024 This study examines the impact of an online math learning program on third through fifth grade math achievement in Louisiana."}, {"source": "third through fifth grade", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "Louisiana", "target_label": "GPE", "sentence": "Measuring the Efficacy of Zearn Math in Louisiana Shirin Hashim AERA Open, September 2024 This study examines the impact of an online math learning program on third through fifth grade math achievement in Louisiana."}, {"source": "Scott A. Pattison", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Gina Svarovsky", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Gina Svarovsky", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Smirla Ramos Montañez", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Viviana López Burgos", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Viviana López Burgos", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Alicia Santiago", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Alicia Santiago", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Sabrina De Los Santos", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "October 2023", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Family-Centered Research: Reflections From a Zoom-Based Recording Method of Families Learning Together at Home Scott A. Pattison, Gina Svarovsky, Smirla Ramos Montañez, Viviana López Burgos, Alicia Santiago, Sabrina De Los Santos Educational Researcher, October 2023"}, {"source": "Sarah McGrew", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Joel Breakstone", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Civic Online Reasoning Across the Curriculum: Developing and Testing the Efficacy of Digital Literacy Lessons Sarah McGrew, Joel Breakstone AERA Open, June 2023"}, {"source": "Joel Breakstone", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "June 2023", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Civic Online Reasoning Across the Curriculum: Developing and Testing the Efficacy of Digital Literacy Lessons Sarah McGrew, Joel Breakstone AERA Open, June 2023"}, {"source": "Dorottya Demszky", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jing Liu", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Jing Liu", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Heather C. Hill", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Heather C. Hill", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Dan Jurafsky", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Dan Jurafsky", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Chris Piech", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Chris Piech", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "May 2023", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Evidence From a Randomized Controlled Trial in a Large-Scale Online Course Dorottya Demszky, Jing Liu, Heather C. Hill, Dan Jurafsky, Chris Piech Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, May 2023"}, {"source": "Changing Lanes:", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Tamara Clegg", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Tamara Clegg", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Kenna Hernly", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Kenna Hernly", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "June Ahn", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "June Ahn", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jason C. Yip", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Jason C. Yip", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Elizabeth Bonsignore", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Daniel Pauw", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Daniel Pauw", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Caroline Pitt", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "Caroline Pitt", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "American Educational Research Journal", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "American Educational Research Journal", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "April 2023", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Researchers found that M-Powering Teachers improves instructors’ uptake of student contributions by 13% and present suggestive evidence that it also improves students’ satisfaction with the course and assignment completion.\nChanging Lanes: Relational Dispositions That Fuel Community Science Learning Tamara Clegg, Kenna Hernly, June Ahn, Jason C. Yip, Elizabeth Bonsignore, Daniel Pauw, Caroline Pitt American Educational Research Journal, April 2023 Researchers examined a sociotechnical system called Science Everywhere, which invited the broader community to interact with science learning experiences youths shared across home, school, and community settings."}, {"source": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Craig A. Mason", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Craig A. Mason", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Ji-Eun Lee", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Ji-Eun Lee", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Yun-Chen Chan", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Yun-Chen Chan", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Adam Sales", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Adam Sales", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Allison Liu", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Allison Liu", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Shihfen Tu", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Shihfen Tu", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "April 2023", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "The Impacts of Three Educational Technologies on Algebraic Understanding in the Context of COVID-19 Lauren E. Decker-Woodrow, Craig A. Mason, Ji-Eun Lee, Jenny Yun-Chen Chan, Adam Sales, Allison Liu, Shihfen Tu AERA Open, April 2023"}, {"source": "Carla C. Johnson", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Janet B. Walton", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research,"}, {"source": "Janet B. Walton", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Lacey Strickler", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research,"}, {"source": "Lacey Strickler", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jennifer Brammer", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research,"}, {"source": "Jennifer Brammer", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Elliott Review of Educational Research", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Carla C. Johnson, Janet B. Walton, Lacey Strickler, Jennifer Brammer Elliott Review of Educational Research,"}, {"source": "Molly", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "PBS", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "PBS", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Joy Lorenzo Kennedy", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Claire G. Christensen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Claire G. Christensen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Tiffany Salone Maxon", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Sarah Nixon Gerard", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Elisa B. Garcia", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Elisa B. Garcia", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Janna F. Kook", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Janna F. Kook", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Naomi Hupert", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Naomi Hupert", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Phil Vahey", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Phil Vahey", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Shelley Pasnik", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Shelley Pasnik", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "American Educational Research Journal", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "American Educational Research Journal", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "July 2022", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "The Efficacy of Digital Media Resources in Improving Children’s Ability to Use Informational Text: An Evaluation of Molly of Denali From PBS KIDS Joy Lorenzo Kennedy, Claire G. Christensen, Tiffany Salone Maxon, Sarah Nixon Gerard, Elisa B. Garcia, Janna F. Kook, Naomi Hupert, Phil Vahey, Shelley Pasnik American Educational Research Journal, July 2022"}, {"source": "Joan Kang Shin", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jered Borup", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Jered Borup", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Michael K. Barbour", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Michael K. Barbour", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "Rocio V. Quiroga Vales", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "April 2022", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Webinars for English Language Teachers During the Pandemic: Global Perspectives on Transitioning to Remote Online Teaching Joan Kang Shin, Jered Borup, Michael K. Barbour, Rocio V. Quiroga Vales quez AERA Open, April 2022"}, {"source": "COVID", "source_label": "EVENT", "target": "Christopher J. Buttimer", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey."}, {"source": "Christopher J. Buttimer", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey."}, {"source": "Joshua Littenberg-Tobias", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Justin Reich", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey."}, {"source": "Justin Reich", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "January 2022", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey."}, {"source": "January 2022", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "4-month", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Designing Online Professional Learning to Support Educators to Teach for Equity During COVID and Black Lives Matter Christopher J. Buttimer, Joshua Littenberg-Tobias, Justin Reich AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that participants changed their equity mind-sets and self-reported equity practices, and that these changes in attitudes and behaviors persisted—and in some cases increased—on the 4-month follow-up survey."}, {"source": "Anna D. Johnson", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Owen N. Schochet", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Owen N. Schochet", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sherri Castle", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Sherri Castle", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Diane Horm", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Diane Horm", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Deborah A. Phillips", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Deborah A. Phillips", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "January 2022", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "January 2022", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Matthew H. Rafalow", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Cassidy Puckett", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Cassidy Puckett", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "January 2022", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Predictors of First-Grade Teachers’ Teaching-Related Time During COVID-19 Anna D. Johnson, Owen N. Schochet, Sherri Castle, Diane Horm, Deborah A. Phillips AERA Open, January 2022 Researchers found that teachers with higher prepandemic job commitment devoted more overall time to pandemic-induced remote teaching.\nSorting Machines: Digital Technology and Categorical Inequality in Education Matthew H. Rafalow, Cassidy Puckett Educational Researcher, January 2022 Researchers show how educational institutions have long played a role in constructing the value of technologies to different ends, by constructing hierarchies of technological activity, like “vocational” and “academic” computer use, even when strikingly similar."}, {"source": "Susan Kemper Patrick", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jason A. Grissom", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Jason A. Grissom", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "S. Colby Woods", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "S. Colby Woods", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "UrLeaka W. Newsome", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "UrLeaka W. Newsome", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "December 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Broadband Access, District Policy, and Student Opportunities for Remote Learning During COVID-19 School Closures Susan Kemper Patrick, Jason A. Grissom, S. Colby Woods, UrLeaka W. Newsome AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "the COVID-19 Pandemic", "source_label": "EVENT", "target": "Germany", "target_label": "GPE", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Germany", "source_label": "GPE", "target": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Catherine Guzenhauser", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Susanne Enke", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Susanne Enke", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Verena E. Johann", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Verena E. Johann", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Julia Karbach", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Julia Karbach", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Henrik Saalbach", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Henrik Saalbach", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "December 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Parent and Teacher Support of Elementary Students’ Remote Learning During the COVID-19 Pandemic in Germany Catherine Guzenhauser, Susanne Enke, Verena E. Johann, Julia Karbach, Henrik Saalbach AERA Open, December 2021"}, {"source": "Curating Spaces of Connection", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Kara M. Gavin", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices Kara M. Gavin AERA Open, December 2021 Researchers examined ways in which a diverse group of 9- and 10-year-old children resisted the isolating circumstances early in the COVID-19 pandemic through creating and repurposing digital spaces to connect with friends, classmates, and family members."}, {"source": "Kara M. Gavin", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "December 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices Kara M. Gavin AERA Open, December 2021 Researchers examined ways in which a diverse group of 9- and 10-year-old children resisted the isolating circumstances early in the COVID-19 pandemic through creating and repurposing digital spaces to connect with friends, classmates, and family members."}, {"source": "December 2021", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "10-year-old", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Curating Spaces of Connection and Resisting Pandemic Isolation Through Innovative Digital Practices Kara M. Gavin AERA Open, December 2021 Researchers examined ways in which a diverse group of 9- and 10-year-old children resisted the isolating circumstances early in the COVID-19 pandemic through creating and repurposing digital spaces to connect with friends, classmates, and family members."}, {"source": "Stephen J. Aguilar", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Hernan Galperin", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021"}, {"source": "Hernan Galperin", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Clare Baek", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021"}, {"source": "Clare Baek", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Eduardo Gonzalez", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021"}, {"source": "Eduardo Gonzalez", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "November 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Live Instruction Predicts Engagement in K–12 Remote Learning Stephen J. Aguilar, Hernan Galperin, Clare Baek, Eduardo Gonzalez Educational Researcher, November 2021"}, {"source": "Christian Fischer", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Rachel Baker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021"}, {"source": "Rachel Baker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Qiujie Li", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021"}, {"source": "Qiujie Li", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Gabe Avakian Orona", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021"}, {"source": "Gabe Avakian Orona", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Mark Warschauer", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021"}, {"source": "Mark Warschauer", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "November 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "The Relationships of Online Course Taking With College Completion and Time-to-Degree Christian Fischer, Rachel Baker, Qiujie Li, Gabe Avakian Orona, Mark Warschauer Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, November 2021"}, {"source": "Remote Learning", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "Kate Henley", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Remote Learning, COVID-19, and Children With Disabilities Kate Henley Averett AERA Open, November 2021 Researchers found that most, but not all, families struggled with remote learning, both when children’s specific needs while learning at home differed from their needs at school, and when schools failed to provide adequate accommodations and services remotely."}, {"source": "Kate Henley", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "November 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Remote Learning, COVID-19, and Children With Disabilities Kate Henley Averett AERA Open, November 2021 Researchers found that most, but not all, families struggled with remote learning, both when children’s specific needs while learning at home differed from their needs at school, and when schools failed to provide adequate accommodations and services remotely."}, {"source": "Houston", "source_label": "GPE", "target": "Texas", "target_label": "GPE", "sentence": "Factors Influencing COVID-19 Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021"}, {"source": "Texas", "source_label": "GPE", "target": "Julia Szabo", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Factors Influencing COVID-19 Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021"}, {"source": "Julia Szabo", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "October 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Factors Influencing COVID-19 Schooling Decisions Among Latinx Families in Houston, Texas Julia Szabo AERA Open, October 2021"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Shantell Griffith", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Shantell Griffith", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Oscar Delaney", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Oscar Delaney", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Nicola Rose Harris", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Nicola Rose Harris", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Taren Sanders", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Taren Sanders", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Philip Parker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Borja del Pozo Cruz", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Borja del Pozo Cruz", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Chris Lonsdale", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Review of Educational Research", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Review of Educational Research", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "October 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Multimedia Design for Learning: An Overview of Reviews With Meta-Meta-Analysis Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Nicola Rose Harris, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, October 2021"}, {"source": "Ido Davidesco", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Camillia Matuk", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Camillia Matuk", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Dana Bevilacqua", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Dana Bevilacqua", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "David Poeppel", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "David Poeppel", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Suzanne Dikker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Suzanne Dikker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "July 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Neuroscience Research in the Classroom: Portable Brain Technologies in Education Research Ido Davidesco, Camillia Matuk, Dana Bevilacqua, David Poeppel, Suzanne Dikker Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Angela L. Duckworth", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Tim Kautz", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Tim Kautz", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Amy Defnet", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Amy Defnet", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Emma Satlof-Bedrick", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sean Talamas", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Sean Talamas", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Benjamin Lira", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Benjamin Lira", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Laurence Steinberg", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Laurence Steinberg", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "July 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Students Attending School Remotely Suffer Socially, Emotionally, and Academically Angela L. Duckworth, Tim Kautz, Amy Defnet, Emma Satlof-Bedrick, Sean Talamas, Benjamin Lira, Laurence Steinberg Educational Researcher, July 2021"}, {"source": "Deoksoon Kim", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Stanton Wortham", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Stanton Wortham", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Katrina Borowiec", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Katrina Borowiec", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Drina Kei Yatsu", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Samantha Ha", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Samantha Ha", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Stephanie Carroll", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Stephanie Carroll", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Lizhou Wang", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Lizhou Wang", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Julie Kim", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Julie Kim", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "May 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Formative Education Online: Teaching the Whole Person During the Global COVID-19 Pandemic Deoksoon Kim, Stanton Wortham, Katrina Borowiec, Drina Kei Yatsu, Samantha Ha, Stephanie Carroll, Lizhou Wang, Julie Kim AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "May 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "A Remote Instructor Like Me: Student–Teacher Congruence in Online, High School Courses Jennifer Darling-Aduana AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Stephanie Riegg Cellini", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Hernando Grueso", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "Hernando Grueso", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "May 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Student Learning in Online College Programs Stephanie Riegg Cellini, Hernando Grueso AERA Open, May 2021"}, {"source": "SENA", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "Colombia", "target_label": "GPE", "sentence": "Researchers found that while online students perform significantly worse than on-campus students on exit exams in private institutions, they perform better in SENA—the main public vocational institution in Colombia."}, {"source": "Carolyn J. Heinrich", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jennifer Darling", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Carolyn J. Heinrich, Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, March 2021"}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "March 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Carolyn J. Heinrich, Jennifer Darling-Aduana Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, March 2021"}, {"source": "Jane Lee", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Taren Sanders", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Taren Sanders", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Devan Antczak", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Devan Antczak", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Rhiannon Parker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Rhiannon Parker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Michael Noetel", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Philip Parker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Chris Lonsdale", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Review of Educational Research", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Review of Educational Research", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "March 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Influences on User Engagement in Online Professional Learning: A Narrative Synthesis and Meta-Analysis Jane Lee, Taren Sanders, Devan Antczak, Rhiannon Parker, Michael Noetel, Philip Parker, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, March 2021"}, {"source": "Michael Noetel", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Shantell Griffith", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Shantell Griffith", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Oscar Delaney", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Oscar Delaney", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Taren Sanders", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Taren Sanders", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Philip Parker", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Philip Parker", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Borja del Pozo Cruz", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Borja del Pozo Cruz", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Chris Lonsdale", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Chris Lonsdale", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Review of Educational Research", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "Review of Educational Research", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "February 2021", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Michael Noetel, Shantell Griffith, Oscar Delaney, Taren Sanders, Philip Parker, Borja del Pozo Cruz, Chris Lonsdale Review of Educational Research, February 2021"}, {"source": "When Logics Collide: Implementing", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Iris Daruwala", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020"}, {"source": "Iris Daruwala", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Shani Bretas", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020"}, {"source": "Shani Bretas", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Douglas D. Ready", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020"}, {"source": "Douglas D. Ready", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "September 2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "When Logics Collide: Implementing Technology-Enabled Personalization in the Age of Accountability Iris Daruwala, Shani Bretas, Douglas D. Ready Educational Researcher, September 2020"}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling-Aduana", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Carolyn Heinrich", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access in High Schools Jennifer Darling-Aduana, Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher, June 2020 Findings from fixed effects models indicate improved access to advanced courses and higher ACT scores among students enrolled in telepresence courses."}, {"source": "Carolyn Heinrich", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "June 2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "The Potential of Telepresence for Increasing Advanced Course Access in High Schools Jennifer Darling-Aduana, Carolyn Heinrich Educational Researcher, June 2020 Findings from fixed effects models indicate improved access to advanced courses and higher ACT scores among students enrolled in telepresence courses."}, {"source": "Julie Cohen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Vivian Wong", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020"}, {"source": "Vivian Wong", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020"}, {"source": "Anandita Krishnamachari", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Rebekah Berlin", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020"}, {"source": "Rebekah Berlin", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "February 2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Teacher Coaching in a Simulated Environment Julie Cohen, Vivian Wong, Anandita Krishnamachari, Rebekah Berlin Educational Evaluation and Policy Analysis, February 2020"}, {"source": "Justin Paulsen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Alexander C. McCormick", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Reassessing Disparities in Online Learner Student Engagement in Higher Education Justin Paulsen, Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher, January 2020"}, {"source": "Alexander C. McCormick", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "January 2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Reassessing Disparities in Online Learner Student Engagement in Higher Education Justin Paulsen, Alexander C. McCormick Educational Researcher, January 2020"}, {"source": "Susan B. Neuman", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Kathleen Roskos", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Kathleen Roskos", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Screens, Apps, and Digital Books for Young Children: The Promise of Multimedia Adriana G. Bus, Susan B. Neuman, Kathleen Roskos AERA Open, 2020"}, {"source": "Escribo", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "Americo N. Amorim", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Americo N. Amorim", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Lieny Jeon", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Lieny Jeon", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Yolanda Abel", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Yolanda Abel", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Eduardo F. Felisberto", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Natália Martins Dias", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Natália Martins Dias", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "2020", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "2020", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "3 months", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Using Escribo Play Video Games to Improve Phonological Awareness, Early Reading, and Writing in Preschool Americo N. Amorim, Lieny Jeon, Yolanda Abel, Eduardo F. Felisberto, Leopoldo N. F. Barbosa, Natália Martins Dias Educational Researcher, 2020 The results indicate that the experimental classrooms that used the 20 games for 3 months gained 68% in their reading scores compared to control classrooms."}, {"source": "Jennifer Darling", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "November 2019", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Behavioral Engagement Shifts Among At-Risk High School Students Enrolled in Online Courses Jennifer Darling-Aduana AERA Open, November 2019"}, {"source": "Jeffrey A. Greene", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Nikki G. Lobczowski", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Rebekah Freed", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Rebekah Freed", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Brian M. Cartiff", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Brian M. Cartiff", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Cynthia Demetriou", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Cynthia Demetriou", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "A. T. Panter", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "A. T. Panter", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "American Educational Research Journal", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "American Educational Research Journal", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "July 2019", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Effects of a Science of Learning Course on College Students’ Learning With a Computer Jeffrey A. Greene, Nikki G. Lobczowski, Rebekah Freed, Brian M. Cartiff, Cynthia Demetriou, A. T. Panter American Educational Research Journal, July 2019"}, {"source": "Dolores Perin", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education", "target_label": "ORG", "sentence": "Teaching Academically Underprepared Postsecondary Students Dolores Perin, Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education, May 2019 This chapter discusses approaches to the teaching of academically underprepared postsecondary students and how teaching might be changed to improve student outcomes."}, {"source": "Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education", "source_label": "ORG", "target": "May 2019", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Teaching Academically Underprepared Postsecondary Students Dolores Perin, Jodi Patrick Holschuh Review of Research in Education, May 2019 This chapter discusses approaches to the teaching of academically underprepared postsecondary students and how teaching might be changed to improve student outcomes."}, {"source": "Rickles", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Heppen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Heppen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Allensworth", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Allensworth", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Sorensen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Sorensen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Walters", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Walters", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "2018", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "2018", "source_label": "DATE", "target": "Jordan Rickles", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Jordan Rickles", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jessica B. Heppen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Jessica B. Heppen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Elaine Allensworth", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Elaine Allensworth", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Nicholas Sorensen", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Nicholas Sorensen", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Kirk Walters", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "Kirk Walters", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "May 2019", "target_label": "DATE", "sentence": "Response to Technical Comment on Rickles, Heppen, Allensworth, Sorensen, and Walters (2018) Jordan Rickles, Jessica B. Heppen, Elaine Allensworth, Nicholas Sorensen, Kirk Walters Educational Researcher, May 2019"}, {"source": "An Efficacy Study of a Digital Core Curriculum for Grade 5 Mathematics", "source_label": "WORK_OF_ART", "target": "Nicole Shechtman", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "An Efficacy Study of a Digital Core Curriculum for Grade 5 Mathematics Nicole Shechtman, Jeremy Roschelle, Mingyu Feng, Corinne Singleton AERA Open, 2019"}, {"source": "Nicole Shechtman", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Jeremy Roschelle", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "An Efficacy Study of a Digital Core Curriculum for Grade 5 Mathematics Nicole Shechtman, Jeremy Roschelle, Mingyu Feng, Corinne Singleton AERA Open, 2019"}, {"source": "Jeremy Roschelle", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Mingyu Feng", "target_label": "PERSON", "sentence": "An Efficacy Study of a Digital Core Curriculum for Grade 5 Mathematics Nicole Shechtman, Jeremy Roschelle, Mingyu Feng, Corinne Singleton AERA Open, 2019"}, {"source": "Mingyu Feng", "source_label": "PERSON", "target": "Corinne 